<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About-rsses on Andrea’s Italian</title>
    <link>http://andreasitalian.com/about/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in About-rsses on Andrea’s Italian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://andreasitalian.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://andreasitalian.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andreasitalian.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://andreasitalian.com/images/special-place.jpg#alignleft&#34; alt=&#34;Sepcial Place&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrea’s Italian&lt;/strong&gt; is a classic Italian Restaurant with comfortable neighborhood charm and destination-caliber
cuisine. Using the best available local ingredients and property-grown organic herbs and vegetables, the daily
changing menu features soulful classics of Italy Country, simply and earnestly prepared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After 20 years of building successful restaurant, Alfonso Carmona has cut quite a wide swath in the culinary landscape.
With Andrea’s, he makes his definitive season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I’m not trying to build a new empire here,”&lt;/em&gt; says Alfonso.
This is just all of my experience wrapped into four walls. My hope is that it will be a place my friends and family feel comfortable in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of people across the city have enjoyed visiting &lt;strong&gt;Andreas’s Italian&lt;/strong&gt; restaurants, though many
are likely to recognize the establishments before they recognize the man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alfonso determined to reopen the facility with modest but substantive changes to the menu and atmosphere. He found
and retained the best people on the staff, most of whom had over 20 years experience, and started to rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andreas’s commitment is to consistently deliver good food at a fair price quickly and efficiently with a great attitude.
He has staked his very life and livelihood in this venture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://andreasitalian.com/images/gl_AR8E8850.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Andrea’s Italian&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>